Guide to the National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- REPORTS, 1919-1943; SERIES XI (Box-folder 11/10-11/26, 11/28, 11/31)
  - National MEBA, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Report of National President to 69th National Convention, 1945 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Changes in Membership, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - CIO, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - Trustees etc., 1919-1921 (Box-folder 11/28)
  - Maritime Federation-Voice, 1936 (Box-folder 11/31)
  - Assorted Reports, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 11/13)
- CONSTITUTION (By Laws and Amendments), 1926-1948; SERIES XII (Box-folder 11/30-11/32, 11/34,11/ 36-11/39)
  - Constitution (and amendments), 1931 (Box-folder 11/30)
  - By Laws, 1931-1940, 1948 (Box-folder 11/31)
  - By Laws, 1931-1940, 1948 (Box-folder 11/32)
  - By Laws, 1931-1940, 1948 (Box-folder 11/38)
  - Formation-Marine Federation of the Pacific Coast, 1935 (Box-folder 11/34)
  - MEBA No 38 (Seattle) (Box-folder 11/36)
  - Info for By Laws, 1926 (Box-folder 11/37)
  - National MEBA, circa 1934 (Box-folder 11/39)
- LEGAL MATERIALS, 1933-1944; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 11/40-11/43, 11/45)
  - Amicus Curiae (Kenneth Durhem), circa 1936 (Box-folder 11/40)
  - Briefs etc., 1933-1936 (Box-folder 11/41)
  - Employee Dismissal Brief, 1939 (Box-folder 11/42)
  - Before the War Shipping Board, National War Labor Board, Union's Closing Brief, 1944 (Box-folder 11/43)
  - Assorted Federal Boards, 1935-1940 (Box-folder 11/45)
- RESOLUTIONS, 1935-1942; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 11/46-11/47)
  - Resolutions, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 11/46)
  - Resolutions, 1935-1942 (Box-folder 11/47)
- APPLICATIONS - (For Membership and Withdrawal), 1924-1942; SERIES XV (Box-folder 12/40-12/41 13)
  - Assorted Applications, 1924-1932 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Assorted Applications, 1931, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Assorted Applications, 1931-1942 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Assorted Applications, 1933-1940 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Transfer and Withdrawal, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Assorted Applications, 1934-1937 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Transfer and Withdrawal, 1935 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - for Retirement, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Paid in Full, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Transfer and Withdrawal, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 12/10-11)
  - Rejected, 1938 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Partially Paid-Nothing Paid, 1934-1937 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Assorted Applications, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Part Paid, 1929-1938 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Transfer and Withdrawal, 1928-1934 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Retirement and Withdrawal, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - for Transfers, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - for Transfer and Withdrawal Cards, 1928 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Paid in Full, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - for Reinstatement, 1932-1935 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - for Transfer and Withdrawal Cards, 1927 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Membership Completed, 1928-1930 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Paid, 1929-1933 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - Assorted Applications, 1940 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Part Paid, 1935 (Box-folder 12/26)
  - for Reinstatement, 1927, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 12/27)
  - for Reinstatement, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - for Reinstatement, 1937 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - for withdrawal card, 1926, 1938 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - Questions and Exams, 1932, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 12/32)
  - Questions and Exams, 1932, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 12/33)
  - Questions and Exams, 1932, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 12/34)
  - Questions and Exams, 1932, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 12/35)
  - Questions and Exams, 1932, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 12/36)
  - Questions and Exams, 1932, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 12/37)
  - Questions and Exams, 1932, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 12/38)
  - Questions and Answers-Chief of Ocean (Box-folder 12/39)
- SAILORS' SNUG HAVEN, 1934; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 12/29)
- TECHNICAL MATERIALS - (Drawings and Printed Matter), 1947; SERIES XVII (Box-folder 12-13)
  - United States Coast Guard-Proposed Amendments to Marine Engineering Regulations and Material Specifications, 1947 (Box-folder 12/40)
  - Agreement with War Shipping Administration, 1947 (Box-folder 12/41)
  - Oversized Ship Diagrams (Box-folder 13)